Guide to the Creative Time Records MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Exhibitions and Projects, 1974-2012; 204.08 Linear Feet in 19 record cartons, 75 manuscript boxes, 275 jewel cases, 22 box binders, 8 oversized flat boxes, 9 oversized folders, 5 shared record cartons, 2 tall manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 1 shared flat box, and 1 shared casset
  - What's in a Flame? by Cathy Quinn, November-December 1989
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 3, Folder 113, Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 141, Folder 6-7)
    - Slides (Box 119, Folder Sleeve 14)
  - Visual AIDS: Day Without Art -- Programs and Press, December 1989 (Box 3, Folder 114, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Press -- General, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 115-116)
  - All people with AIDS are innocent by Gran Fury -- Negative, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Rumi's Room, XYZOMPANTLI, Organikwars, Softwars Cardpost, El Labertinto de Kurtycz, Maiz, Mi Casa, Agrest, and Others -- Mail Art, Performances, and Publications by Marcos Kurtycz, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 58-89)
  - Organikwars Hocker Fold-Out Artwork by Marcos Kurtycz, Undated (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Demolish the Wall of Censorship by Multiple Artists -- Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints, March 1990 (Box 107, Folder 1-3)
  - Creative Time at Dixon Place by Multiple Artists, April 1990
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 120, Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 107, Folder 4-6)
    - Slides (Box 119, Folder Sleeve 20)
  - The Black Sheep by Karen Finley, May 1990
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 3, Folder 121, Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 107, Folder 7-8)
    - Slides (Box 119, Folder Sleeve 20)
  - The Wilds and the Deep by Martha Fleming and Lyne Lapointe -- Battery Maritime Building, May 1990
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 122-123, Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Prints (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Slides (Box 119, Folder Sleeves 21-24)
  - Art in the Anchorage 7 by Multiple Artists, July-October 1990
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 124-126, Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 107, Folder 10-12, Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Slides (Box 119, Folder Sleeves 25-31)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Karen Finley -- 3 Parables and 2 Testimonies (Box 145, Dvd 179.0192)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Karen Finley -- 3 Parables and 2 Testimonies (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0191)
  - Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors by Multiple Artists, August 1990
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 127, Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 108, Folder 2-4)
    - Slides (Box 120, Folder 1-3)
  - Surgeon General's Warning by Beth B., September-November 1990
    - Press, Poster, and Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 128, Box 38, Folder 11, Flat-file-folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 108, Folder 5-6)
    - Slides (Box 120, Folder Sleeve 6)
  - The Bowery Concert by Multiple Artists, September 1990
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 129, Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 108, Folder 7-9)
    - Slides (Box 120, Folder Sleeves 4-5)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- 4 PM Show (Box 148, Dvd 179.0417)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- 4 PM Show (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0416)
  - Press -- General, October 1990 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Carbon Monoxide Is a Lethal Gas by Hilja Keading, October-November 1990
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 131, Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 108, Folder 12-14)
    - Slides (Box 120, Folder Sleeves 7-8)
  - Love of a Poet by John Kelly -- Battery Maritime Building, October 1990
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 134, Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Prints and Contact Sheets (Box 108, Folder 10-11)
    - Slides (Box 120, Folder Sleeves 7-8)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 149, Dvd 179.0437)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0436)
  - Day Without Art: Electric Blanket by Multiple Artists, December 1990
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 135, Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Prints (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- HIV TV -- Swarthmore College (Box 150, Dvd 179.0521)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- HIV TV -- Swarthmore College (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0520)
  - XYZOMPANTLI by Marcos Kurtycz -- Performance Poster, December 1990 (Box Shared Fales 081, Folder 5)
  - "A Threnody for Street Kids" Brochure by David Levi Strauss, circa 1990 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Press -- General, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Citywide -- Correspondence and Guidelines, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 140, Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Event Mailing and Press, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 141-142)
  - Visualize This by Nancy Burson with Kunio Nagashima, April 1991
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 145-146, Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Posters (Flat-file-folder 10, Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
    - Negatives and Prints (Box 108, Folder 16-17)
    - Slides (Box 120, Folder Sleeve 27)
  - Angels Have Been Sent to Me by Jerri Allyn with Helen Thorington, May 1991
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 147, Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 108, Folder 18-20)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Part 1 -- English and Spanish (Box 145, Cd 179.0103)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Part 2 -- English and Spanish (Box 145, Cd 179.0104)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- English and Spanish (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0102)
  - Black Works by Station Opera House -- Co-Presented by The Kitchen, May 1991
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 148-149, Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 108, Folder 21-22)
    - Slides (Box 120, Folder Sleeves 10-12)
  - Choice, Keep Abortion Legal Starring the Most Exciting Women in Music: A Public Service Announcement by Juliet Cuming, June 1991
    - Correspondence and Press (Box 3, Folder 150-151, Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 108, Folder 25-27)
  - Not Just the Parade, Time to Get Paid and First on the Front Line Last on the Payroll Line by Algernon Miller, June 1991
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 152, Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Negatives and Prints (Box 108, Folder 23-24)
    - Slides (Box 121, Folder Sleeve 1)
  - The Honeymoon Project by Miralda, June 1991
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 153, Box 21, Folder 263, Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 108, Folder 28, Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Slides (Box 120, Folder Sleeves 13-26)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Jordi Torrent -- "Honeymoon" (Box 149, Dvd 179.0439)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Miralda -- The Honeymoon Project -- Cued for 10 Minute Viewing Segment, Parts 1-2 (Box 145, Dvd 179.0142)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Jordi Torrent -- "Monuments in Love" (Box 145, Dvd 179.0140)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Miralda -- The Honeymoon Project -- Cued for 10 Minute Viewing Segment, Parts 1-2 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0141)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Jordi Torrent -- "Honeymoon" (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0139)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Jordi Torrent -- "Monuments in Love" (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0139)
  - Suz/o/Suz by La Fura Dels Baus -- Co-Presented by The Kitchen, P.S. 122, and The New York International Festival of the Arts, June 1991
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 154, Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 109, Folder 2-3)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 146, Dvd 179.0186)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0185)
  - Memories of New York Chinatown by Tomie Arai, June 1991
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 155, Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Contact Sheet and Prints (Box 109, Folder 4-5)
    - Slides (Box 120, Folder Sleeve 28)
  - Art in the Anchorage 8 by Multiple Artists, July-September 1991
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 156-157, Box 4, Folder 212, Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 109, Folder 6-11)
    - Slides (Box 121, Folder Sleeves 2-11)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Dumb Type -- pH (1990) and Pleasure Life (1988) (Box 150, Dvd 179.0541)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Dumb Type -- pH -- Kyoto Municipal Museum of the Arts, Institute Contemporary Arts, Nagoya (1991) (Box 150, Dvd 179.0537)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Dumb Type -- pH (Box 150, Dvd 179.0539)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Dumb Type -- pH (Box 150, Dvd 179.0543)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Guy Yarden (Box 144, Cd 179.0030)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Arthur Russell (Box 144, Cd 179.0028)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Bosho (Box 144, Cd 179.0026)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Hugo Largo (Box 144, Cd 179.0032)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Linda Fisher (Box 144, Cd 179.0024)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Linda Fisher (Box 145, Cd 179.0110)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Manhattan Marimba Quartet (Box 144, Cd 179.0058)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Manhattan Marimba Quartet (Box 144, Cd 179.0056)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Guy Yarden (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0029)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Arthur Russell (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0027)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Bosho (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0025)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Hugo Largo (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0031)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Linda Fisher (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0023)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Linda Fisher (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0109)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Manhattan Marimba Quartet (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0057)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Manhattan Marimba Quartet (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0055)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Dumb Type -- pH (1990) and Pleasure Life (1988) (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0540)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Dumb Type -- pH (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0538)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Dumb Type -- pH (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0542)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Dumb Type -- pH -- Kyoto Municipal Museum of the Arts, Institute Contemporary Arts, Nagoya (1991) (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0536)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Toni Dove -- Mesmer, Secrets of the Human Frame (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0670)
  - Skin by Paula Josa-Jones and Pauline Oliveros, August 1991
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 3, Folder 158, Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 109, Folder 12-13)
    - Slides (Box 121, Folder Sleeves 12-14)
  - Wigstock by Multiple Artists, September 1991
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 159, Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Prints (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Slides (Box 121, Folder Sleeve 15)
  - Masterpieces Without the Director by Spencer Finch and Paul Ramírez-Jonas, September 1991
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 160, Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 109, Folder 15-17)
    - Slides (Box 121, Folder Sleeves 16-18)
  - Clean Needles Save Lives: Drug Users Doing It for Ourselves by Multiple Artists, October 1991
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 4, Folder 161, Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 150, Dvd 179.0527)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- "Needle Exchange" (Box 150, Dvd 179.0529)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0526)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "Needle Exchange" (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0528)
  - As a Dream That Vanishes (A Meditation on the Harvest of a Lifetime) by Merry Conway, Noni Pratt, and Albert Ratcliffe, October-November 1991
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 4, Folder 162, Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 109, Folder 18-19)
    - Slides (Box 121, Folder Sleeves 19-21)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- As a Dream That Vanishes (A Meditation on the Harvest of a Lifetime) and In the Eye of the Beholder (1988) (Box 149, Dvd 179.0461)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- As a Dream That Vanishes (A Meditation on the Harvest of a Lifetime) and In the Eye of the Beholder (1988) (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0460)
  - The Fear of Disclosure Project: (In)Visible Women by Multiple Artists, December 1991
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 4, Folder 163, Folder 172, Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Prints (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Ellen Spiro and Marina Alvarez (Box 149, Dvd 179.0445)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Ellen Spiro and Marina Alvarez (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0444)
  - Our Voices: Our Songs by Lavender Light Gospel Choir, December 1991
    - Programs, Press, and Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 164, Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 133, Folder 2-3)
    - Slides (Box 121, Folder Sleeves 22-23)
  - Citywide -- Guidelines and Correspondence, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 165, Folder 167, Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Press -- General, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - The Domestic Violence Milk Carton Project by Peggy Diggs, January-February 1992
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 173-175, Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 133, Folder 5-7)
    - Slides (Box 121, Folder Sleeves 25-26)
  - Use Mass Transit 1 by Roger Shimomura, January-February 1992
    - Correspondence, Press, and Programs (Box 4, Folder 176, Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Print (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Slides (Box 121, Folder Sleeve 24)
  - Roy Cohn/Jack Smith by Ron Vawter, January-February 1992
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 177, Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Print (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Slides (Box 121, Folder Sleeve 27)
  - Private/Public by Multiple Artists, March-May 1992
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 178, Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 133, Folder 10-11)
    - Slides (Box 121, Folder Sleeves 28-29)
  - Transitions, Inc. by Danny Tisdale, May 1992
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 179, Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 133, Folder 12-14)
    - Slides (Box 122, Folder Sleeve 1)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 149, Dvd 179.0441)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0440)
  - Sacrificial Ornament by Spring Hurlbut -- Co-Presented by Municipal Art Society, May-June 1992
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 180-181, Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Poster (Flat-file-folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 133, Folder 15-16)
    - Slides (Box 122, Folder Sleeve 2)
  - Art in the Anchorage 9: Women's Action Coalition by Multiple Artists, July-September 1992
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 182, Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 133, Folder 18-19)
    - Slides (Box 122, Folder Sleeves 3-14)
  - A Surreal Soap Opera by Victoria Bugbee and Company -- Co-Presented by Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors, August 1992
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 183, Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 133, Folder 20-21)
    - Slides (Box 122, Folder Sleeves 15-16)
  - Accountability? by Dinh Le, October 1992
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 185, Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 133, Folder 22-23)
    - Slides (Box 122, Folder Sleeve 18)
  - Two Spirits Speak Out by Multiple Artists, November 1992
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 187, Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints -- Glenn Belverio and Duncan Elliott (Box 133, Folder 24-25)
    - Slides (Box 122, Folder Sleeve 17)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Glenn Belverio (Box 147, Dvd 179.0264)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Glenn Belverio (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0263)
  - Use Mass Transit 2 by Jerri Allyn, December 1992-January 1993
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 188, Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Print (Box 134, Folder 1-3)
    - Slides (Box 122, Folder Sleeve 26)
  - Day Without Art: We Interrupt This Program... by Multiple Artists, December 1992
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 189, Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Poster (Flat-file-folder 10)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 133, Folder 26-27)
    - Slides (Box 122, Folder Sleeves 19-23)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Maria Perez -- "Safersister" Public Service Announcements -- English and Spanish (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0682)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Thomas Harris -- "AIDs and Art" -- The Eleventh Hour, #266 -- WNET Thirteen (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0685)
  - The Fear of Disclosure Project: Non, Je Ne Regrette Rien (No Regret) by Marlon T. Riggs, 1992
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 190, Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Prints (Box 133, Folder 17)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 149, Dvd 179.0447)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0446)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0668)
  - Press -- General, February 1992
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- "Masterpieces Without The Director" -- Milk Carton Project -- WBAI (Box 144, Cd 179.0054)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- "Masterpieces Without The Director" -- Milk Carton Project -- WBAI (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0053)
  - Higher Ground by Sarah Skaggs Dance Company, January 1993
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 193, Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 134, Folder 4-5)
    - Slides (Box 122, Folder Sleeves 24-25)
  - Victory Music Series by Multiple Artists, April 1993
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 194, Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 134, Folder 6-8)
    - Slides (Box 122, Folder Sleeves 27-29)
  - Hairy Tales by Debra Levine, April 1993
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 195, Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 134, Folder 9-11)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 149, Dvd 179.0443)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0442)
  - Art in the Anchorage 10 by Elizabeth Streb and Ringside, June-September 1993
    - Electronic Records, cuid40866
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 196-199, Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 134, Folder 12-14)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Elizabeth Streb -- "Dyke TV" -- Episode 19 (Box 150, Dvd 179.0505)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Ringside (Box 151, Dvd 179.0696)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Elizabeth Streb and Ringside, "Kid Action" (Box 146, Dvd 179.0244)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Elizabeth Streb -- "Dyke TV" -- Episode 19 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0504)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Ringside Choreography -- Excerpts (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0681)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Elizabeth Streb and Ringside, "Kid Action" (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0243)
  - In Honor of Allen R. Schindler by Bureau (Marlene McCarty and Donald Moffett), July 1993
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 200, Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Negatives and Prints (Box 134, Folder 15-16)
    - Slides (Box 123, Folder 23)
  - 42nd Street Art Project by Multiple Artists, July-November 1993
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 201-206, Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 134, Folder 17-19)
    - Slides (Box 123, Folder Sleeves 1-22)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Interviews (Box 149, Dvd 179.0487)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- TV Coverage (New York 1, MTV News, and Others) (Box 149, Dvd 179.0473)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- TV Coverage and Interviews (Box 148, Dvd 179.0398)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Interviews (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0486)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- TV Coverage (New York 1, MTV News, and Others) (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0472)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- TV Coverage and Interviews (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0397)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- TV Coverage and Interviews (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0399)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- TV Coverage and Interviews (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0400)
  - Universal Family Album by Max Below and Kim Irwin -- Co-Presented with Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors, August 1993
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 207, Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 134, Folder 20-22)
    - Slides (Box 123, Folder Sleeves 24-25)
  - Underdevelopment in Progress/500 Years by Vistas Latinas (Ana Ferrer and Kukuli Velarde), September-October 1993
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 186, Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 135)
    - Slides (Box 123, Folder Sleeves 32-33)
  - Dyke TV: Weekly Art Segment by Multiple Artists, 1993
    - Prints (Box 134, Folder 23)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Dyke TV -- Arts Compilation (Box 150, Dvd 179.0509)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Dyke TV -- Episodes 1 and 3 (Box 150, Dvd 179.0507)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Dyke TV -- Arts Compilation (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0508)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Dyke TV -- Episodes 1 and 3 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0506)
  - Day Without Art: We Interrupt This Program... by Multiple Artists, December 1993
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 135, Folder 4-5)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Nelson Rodriguez -- HIV: A Home Video (Drafts #2 and #4) and 13 Years (Draft #3) (Box 150, Dvd 179.0519)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Nelson Rodriguez -- HIV: A Home Video (Drafts #2 and #4) and 13 Years (Draft #3) (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0518)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- We Interrupt This Program -- Directed by Mary Ellen Strom and Produced by Barbara L. Tsumagari (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0674)
  - Just Outside the City -- Programs and Press, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 209)
  - Crossed Masks: A Return to the Source by Renee Valarie Cox -- Unrealized Project -- Correspondence and Proposal, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Body Politics by Multiple Artists, February 1994
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 5, Folder 214, Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 135, Folder 6-7)
    - Slides (Box 124, Folder Sleeves 1-3)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Martha Wilson, Joyce Scott, Blondell Cummings, Reno, and Carnival Knowledge (Box 150, Dvd 179.0513)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Martha Wilson, Mary Ellen Strom, Peggy Pettitt, and Holly Hughes (Box 148, Dvd 179.0384)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Martha Wilson, Joyce Scott, Blondell Cummings, Reno, and Carnival Knowledge (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0512)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Martha Wilson, Mary Ellen Strom, Peggy Pettitt, and Holly Hughes (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0383)
  - Mass Transit 3: Hey Bozo, Use Mass Transit by G. H. Hovagimyan, May 1994
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 5, Folder 215, Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Slides (Box 124, Folder Sleeves 4-5)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- TV Coverage (Box 148, Dvd 179.0252)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- TV Coverage (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0251)
  - The Fear of Disclosure Project: Out in Silence and Not a Simple Story by Christine Choy, June 1994